[Music]
n
remember four walls around me a TV to
keep me compan
[Music]
sitting here all by myself my mind
seting on the shelf and next to
[Music]
me The Greatest Story Ever Told a part
of life put on hold I put on
[Music]
hold but
remember
[Music]
oh
remember I passed a church the other day
I heard a lot of people say and you love
[Music]
me it made me think when I was young I
learned you gave your only son Set Me
Free oh I let my life get in the way but
now I feel the need to pray the need to
[Music]
pray but I
remember
remember as I look back through all my
years I can't stop the flood of
tears I
forgot and what it is to
give give myself up to
you but now I
remember
[Music]
I
remember
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
I